Play It To Death.
Stay Alive is a horror, mystery film directed by William Brent Bell.
After the brutal death of a friend, a group of friends find themselves in possession of a video-game called
"Stay Alive," a blood-curdling true story of a 17th century noblewoman known as the Blood Countess.
After playing the game when they know they shouldn't, however, the friends
realize that once they die in the game — they die for real!
Hutch, played by Jon Foster.
Abigail, played by Samaire Armstrong.
Swink, played by Frankie Muniz.
October, played by Sophia Bush.
Phineus, played by Jimmi Simpson.
Miller Banks, played by Adam Goldberg.
Stay Alive is a 2006 American supernatural techno horror film directed by
William Brent Bell, who co-wrote it with Matthew Peterman.
The film was produced by Joseph McGinty Nichol, and released on March
24, 2006, in the United States by Hollywood Pictures.
The film explores themes of hacker, video game,
virtual reality, virtual fight, baroness.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.